<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
	<properties>
		<title>Module workflow editrecord</title>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="Module workflow editrecord">
			<subsection name="Introduction">
                <p>This module contains a workflow task to edit a record of a directory (from the <code>plugin-directory</code>). The front-office user accesses a page to edit the record, thanks to a link sent by email.
                </p>
			</subsection>
            <subsection name="Usage">
                <p><strong>Configure the workflow task</strong></p>
                <p>The field <code>State after edition</code> corresponds to the target state after the front-office user has edited the record.
                </p>
                <p>The field <code>Default message</code> corresponds to the message displayed in the task form when the back-office user executes the action. 
                The user can modify this message in the form. It is then displayed in the front-office edition page.
                </p>

                <p><strong>Execute an action when the record is edited</strong></p>
                <p>After the submission of the edition by the front-office user, the process calls the first automatic workflow action whose initial state is the state defined in the configuration task.
                </p>
                <p>Thus, to execute a workflow action after the front-office user has submitted the edition of the record:
                    <ul>
                        <li>Create a state in the workflow. This state can be used only for this purpose.</li>
                        <li>In the task configuration, use the created state in the field <code>State after edition</code>.</li>
                        <li>Create an automatic action whose initial state is the created state and the final state is your wanted state.</li>
                        <li>Add your wanted tasks in this action.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>Here is an example:</p>
                <p>States
                    <ul>
                        <li><code>Title</code>: In progress</li>
                        <li><code>Title</code>: Waiting for edition</li>
                        <li><code>Title</code>: Record edited</li>
                    </ul>
                    Actions
                    <ul>
                        <li><code>Title</code>: Ask for record edition. <code>States</code>: In progress -> Waiting for edition. <code>Automatic</code>: no.</li>
                        <li><code>Title</code>: Edit record. <code>States</code>: Record edited -> In progress. <code>Automatic</code>: yes.</li>
                    </ul>
                    Tasks
                    <ul>
                        <li><code>Type</code>: Directory record edition. <code>Action</code>: Ask for record edition. <code>Configuration</code>: <code>State after edition</code> = Record edited</li>
                        <li><code>Type</code>: as you want. <code>Action</code>: Edit record.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            </subsection>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>